http://www.charnvel.co.uk/index.php/terms-of-use

Home/Terms of Use
Terms of Use
IMPORTANT – PLEASE READ
This is the Charnvel website (the "Website" and is operated by Charnvel Ltd. Charnvel Ltd ("Charnvel") has its headquarters offices at Charnvel House, Canterbury Road, Radford, Nottingham, England, NG8 1PQ (Company registration number 2925653, VAT registration number 651 326 554).These terms will apply to all users of the Website. Please read them very carefully.
How You Should Use this Website
Your attention is drawn to these Terms of Use, which explain how this Website should be used. By using this Website, you agree to these Terms of Use. If you do not accept these Terms of Use and do not intend to be bound by them you must not use this Website and should exit it immediately. Your continued use of this Website will constitute acceptance of these Terms.
This Website provides you with information about Charnvel and the products and services which we offer. Always check the validity of all information (drawings calculations etc.) contained within the site by contacting the relevant department.
We reserve the right to alter, delete, adapt, take down or in any other way amend the whole or any part of this Website including any of the content contained on it at any time and without notice. These Terms may change from time to time and you should review this page on a regular basis. If you continue to use the Website after any such amendments have been made you will be deemed to accept those amendments. You may access these Terms at any time by accessing the link to them which appears at the foot of each page of this Website.
This Website is aimed primarily at users in the UK and all communications shall be in English.
Where any user is in breach of these Terms, we may but shall not be required, to provide a warning to such user for failure to comply. Further, we have the right to ban any user from the Website at any time, whether or not any prior warning has been given.
Ownership Rights
All Website design, text, graphics, the selection and arrangement thereof, software compilations, underlying source code, software and images together with all other material on this Website are either owned by Charnvel or used under licence from third party rights owners.
To the extent that any material contained on this Website may be downloaded or printed then such material may be downloaded to a single personal computer only and hard copy portions may be printed solely for your own personal and non-commercial use.Copyright © Charnvel Ltd
All rights reserved.
You acknowledge the intellectual proprietary rights in all content on the Website and you understand that content on this Website is protected by copyright law. Under no circumstances shall you in any way modify, publish, transmit, copy (in whole or in part), distribute or incorporate into any other website or other medium or material, any images which appear on the Website whatsoever.
Links to other websites
This Website may contain links to other websites which may be of interest. All links are provided for your information and convenience only and your use of any such websites shall be subject to any terms, which are on those sites, including any privacy policies. Charnvel does not make any representation or give any warranty about the links, which are provided, to third party sites. Those third parties may offer products or services for sale and if you decide to purchase them, this shall be an arrangement between you and the third party. In no way shall Charnvel be liable for any such products or services and we do not make any representations or give any recommendations in respect of them.
Limitation of Liability and Disclaimer
We make every effort to ensure the information on this Website is accurate. This Website is provided on an "as is" basis which means that you must use the Website exactly as it is provided to you. Charnvel shall not be liable for the accuracy, completeness or appropriateness of any content. It is your responsibility to satisfy yourself that any content or information, which you use from this Website, is suitable for your own particular purposes.
You assume full responsibility for using any information on the Website and you understand and agree that if you use information neither Charnvel nor its employees are responsible or liable for any claim, loss or damage arising from such use. We do not represent or warrant that the information accessible via this Website, is accurate, complete or current nor that this Website will be available, accessible, uninterrupted, timely, secure or operate without error or that it will be free from viruses or other harmful elements.
TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED AT LAW, NEITHER CHARNVEL NOR ANY EMPLOYEE OR REPRESENTATIVE INVOLVED IN THE WEBSITE WILL BE LIABLE WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, STATUTE OR OTHERWISE HOWSOEVER ARISING FOR ANY DAMAGES, LOSSES, COSTS, CLAIMS, LIABILITIES OR EXPENSES ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OF THIS WEBSITE.
THIS EXCLUSION AND LIMITATION OF LIABILITY SHALL APPLY TO ALL DAMAGES, LOSSES, COSTS, CLAIMS, LIABILITIES AND EXPENSES OF ANY KIND WHETHER DIRECT OR INDIRECT, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION LEGAL COSTS OR EXPENSES, DIRECT LOSS OF PROFIT, DIRECT LOSS OF ANTICIPATED SAVINGS, INDIRECT LOSS OF PROFIT, INDIRECT LOSS OF ANTICIPATED SAVINGS, LOSS OF REVENUE, LOSS OF USE OF MONEY, LOSS OF OPPORTUNITY OR LOSS OF OR DAMAGE TO PROPERTY AND/OR ANY WASTED EXPENDITURE OR THIRD PARTY CLAIMS. FOR THE AVOIDANCE OF DOUBT THE LOSSES AS LISTED IN THIS CLAUSE ARE INTENDED TO BE DISTINCT AND SEVERABLE. NOTHING CONTAINED IN THIS CLAUSE SHALL AFFECT YOUR STATUTORY RIGHTS.
Nothing in these Terms shall exclude or limit our liability for death or personal injury caused by our negligence or for fraudulent misrepresentation.
Privacy Policy
We understand the importance of ensuring that we treat your personal information carefully and in confidence. Please refer to our Privacy Policy for details of how we will use your personal data by clicking here. You can also view our Privacy Policy at any time by clicking on the link which appears at the foot of each page of the Website.
Law and Jurisdiction
These Terms and your use of this Website shall be subject to English law and any disputes shall be determined in the English courts.We will not be liable to fulfil any undertaking on our part including where that failure is caused by trade dispute or breakdown of machinery or any other matter outside our control.
If part, or all, of these Terms become void the remaining part of them and any other provisions on the Website which shall form part of these Terms will remain valid and enforceable.
Failure by us to exercise, or delay in our exercising, any right or remedy under these Terms shall not waive any of the rights and remedies available to us.Except as expressly agreed in these Terms a person who is not a party to the Contract shall have no rights pursuant to the Contracts ( Rights of Third Parties ) Act 1999 ( the “Act” ) to enforce any term of the Contract. Any right or remedy of a third party which exists or is available apart from the Act is not affected.Nothing in these Terms shall be construed as establishing or implying a partnership between Charnvel or any member of the Charnvel group of companies and any user of the Website nor shall any relationship of agency be implied.
Tweet
